ONIPEDE SAMSON ADEDAYO

S7/449 F Idowukoya Street Challenge, Ibadan, Oyo State.

Mobile:08168486380|Email:Adedayo142@gmail.com|Linkedln:https://www.linkedin.com/in/samsonadedayo/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Self-motivated **Software Developer** with a high level of experience working on multiple projects, passionate and hardworking with a penchant for meeting deadlines. I have a Bachelor degree in **Mathematics**. I engage in group projects while also freelancing.

Having been doing these for two years, I am Interested in a role with a company that promotes best practices and offers a wealth of customer projects. Also seeking an opportunity to further build a strong skill set while working on multiple projects. With my **JavaScript** skills I have done a Face App, Robot App and a Food Recipe App, Movie APP and many more also some mobile app using **Flutter**. I have gained the needed experience to showcase my skillset in your establishment.

SKILLS

- Knowledge of Computer Programming language.
- Mastery in Html5, Css3, JavaScript, Dart.
- Knowledge of JavaScript library in React.
- Good skills using Flutter for Mobile Development.
- Understanding of Nodejs, PostgreSQL, MySql.
- Google skills.
- Fluent in both English and Yoruba Language.
- Front End Web Developer.
- General Computing.

EXPERIENCE

06/2016 to 05/2017

Budget Planning Assistant

National Youth Service Corps (N.Y.S.C)

IBADAN SOUTH-WEST LOCAL GOVERNMENT COUNCIL

- Review of budget allocated for all other ministries.
- Keeping records of previous budget for future review.
- Final approval of each ministries budget before allocation of funds.

10/2017 to 06/2018

Customer Care Representative/IT Consultant

Vitotek Global Service – IBADAN.

- Helping to resolve any customer complaint.
- Interacts with our customer to provide them with information to address inquiries regarding our services.

09/2018 to 07/2020

Teacher/Tutor

Community Basic Model School Elewura Challenge, IBADAN.

- Teach the learners and put them through in their work.
- Coordinate the class and monitor the learners throughout the activities in the learning environment.

2018 to present

Software Developer (Web and Mobile)

- Creating personal web and mobile application projects.
- Developing responsive website and application using React.
- Developed mobile applications.

EDUCATION

2015 Bachelor of Science: Mathematics (Second Class Division)

Tai Solarin University of Education Ijebu-Ode, Ogun State

2010 Certificate of Higher Education: Science

Hogas International College-Lagos

2004 Primary School Leaving Certificate

Yabtom Nursery and Primary School -Lagos

ACCOMPLISHMENT

- My portfolio website which has some of my projects. https://bit.ly/samsonadedayo
- My GitHub account: https://www.github.com/onipedadedayo142.

VOLUNTEERING & INTEREST

- Google enthusiast.
- Head of IT for a Non-governmental Organization, Information for All Africans Initiative.
- Developed a website for IFAAI, https://www.ifaai.netlify.app.
- Coding.

REFEREES